Guide to the Merle Hoffman Papers, circa 1944-2012 and undated, bulk 1961-2000 RL.00557
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials Series, 1974-1998 and undated, 4 boxes
  - Audio Recordings, 1974-1997 and undated
    - Audiocassettes, 1974-1997 and undated, 62 tapes
      - OR31. Circa 1981, "Channel 4 ed OTC": Editorial on over-the-counter contraceptives (Box AV1)
      - OR32. 1982 Feb. 9, "Q: 'Medicade accepted' (Darcel-Vo)": Choices advertisement, "Medicaid accepted," WWRL radio (Box AV1)
      - OR33. 1982 Apr. 20, "Pat Whitley": Interview on Human Life Amendment with Merle Hoffman and Joe Riley (Box AV1)
      - OR34. 1983 Nov., ":60, 11/83 Yevonne": Choices advertisement (Box AV1)
      - OR35. 1983, "1983 Interview": Interview on Choices and abortion, unidentified radio station (Box AV2)
      - OR36. 1986 Nov. 21, "Karen Thompson": Karen Thompson interview for On the Issues (Box AV2)
      - OR37-38. 1989 Feb. 7, "Barry Gray": Call-in discussion of abortion and Nancy Klein court case, 2 cassettes (Box AV2)
      - OR39. 1991 Jan. 27, "Dr. Lenore Walker/Phyllis Chesler": Lenore Walker and Phyllis Chesler interviews for "pro-therapy article" [ On the Issues?] (Box AV2)
      - OR40. 1993 Oct. 23, "OTI Tape 3": Discussion of On the Issues editorial planning (Box AV2)
      - OR41. 1994 Jan. 26, "Arleen Wurnos [sp?] film dialog"/ "Tribeca Warnos [sp?]": interview on Florida court case (Box AV2)
      - OR42. 1994 Aug. 7, "Broadcast of August 7, 1994": Interview on anti-abortion violence (Box AV2)
      - OR43. 1994 Aug. 31, "Derek McGinty": Interview about On the Issues, unidentified Washington, D.C. radio station (Box AV2)
      - OR45. 1995, "Dead Doctors Don't Lie": Joel Wallach, speech on vitamins and alternative therapies [removed from Operation Rescue files] (Box AV2)
      - OR44. 1997 May 3, "Independent providers' meeting": Meeting (Box AV2)
      - OR45. Undated, "Bill Baird": Bill Baird interview (Box AV2)
      - OR46. Undated, "C": Unidentified woman, second half of interview on life in prison (Box AV2)
      - OR47. Undated, "Choices": Choices advertisement, WRKS radio (Box AV2)
      - OR48. Undated, "Choices 3 spots": Choices advertisements on depression and domestic violence (Box AV2)
      - OR49. Undated, "Choices: 30": Choices advertisement, WPLJ radio (Box AV2)
      - OR50. Undated, "Choices - WKTU-FM": Choices advertisement, WKTU-FM radio (Box AV2)
      - OR51. Undated, "Choices - WKTU-FM (female voice)": Choices advertisement, WKTU-FM radio (Box AV2)
      - OR52. Undated, "Choices - WKTU-FM (male voice)": Choices advertisement, WKTU-FM (Box AV2)
      - OR53-54. Undated, "Debate w/Rev. Dan Fore (Ralph Hart)": Abortion debate with Dan Fore, WMCA radio, 2 cassettes (Box AV2)
      - OR55. Undated, "Hoffman Carl Weiss 9/28": Interview on breast cancer with Merle Hoffman and E. Teeson [sp?], WNYC radio, "Coping through the Day" (Box AV2)
      - OR56. Undated, "Margaret Jones": Interview and call-in discussion on "patient power" (Box AV2)
      - OR57. Undated, "MH and ET - Ray Schnitzer": Call-in discussion of breast cancer with Merle Hoffman and E. Teeson [sp?], WYNC radio, "Health Line" (Box AV2)
      - OR58. Undated, "MH - Interview with Bob Grant": Interview and call-in discussion on "patient power" and abortion, WMCA radio (Box AV2)
      - OR59. Undated, "MH - Lillie Bruck": Interview on Choices and "patient power" (Box AV2)
      - OR60. Undated, "MH-RS interview on women": Ronnie Sandroff [?] interviewing Merle about women in job interviews, for On the Issues (Box AV2)
      - OR61. Undated, "PMS 9/14": Call-in discussion on post-menstrual syndrome with Merle Hoffman, Judy Simmons, and Renny Witt [sp?], WLIB radio (Box AV2)
      - OR62. Undated, "WEVD 'Breast Disease'"/ "Doc - improv": Interview on breast disease, WEVD (side 1), and skits on how to tell partner about pregnancy (side 2) (Box AV2)
    - Audiotapes, 1974
      [Original closed to use. No use copy currently available. Technical Services staff need to produce use copy before contents can be accessed. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use the collection.]
      - Original OR63 (CLOSED TO USE) (Box AV2)
      - OR63. 1974 Nov. 15, "Report on Medicine, Lou Adler and Merle Hoffman", 5 inch reel (Box AV3)
  - Video Recordings, 1980-1998 and undated
    Video recordings include episodes of "On the Issues," Merle Hoffman's cable access television show, and some documentary material on Choices and its patients. Topics include contraception, managed health care, abortion, rape, women in prison and the criminal justice system, censorship, pornography, obesity as a feminist issue, reproductive rights, breast diseases, anti-abortion violence, women in religion, feminism, and domestic violence. Some video recordings are in Ampex format. Arranged by format, then chronologically.
    - Ampex Videotapes, 1980-1986 and undated
      Some titles listed are duplicates also found in the U-Matic videocassettes subgroup.
      - Originals OR64-71 (CLOSED) (Box AV3)
      - OR64. 1980, Over-the-counter (OTC) contraceptives - editorial, Channel 5 (Box AV3)
      - OR65. 1981 June 3, "Weekday" (show #176), on Human Life Amendment (Box AV3)
      - OR66. 1981 Dec. 7, "Abortion: People are Talking," WBZ TV, Boston (Box AV3)
      - OR67. 1981, Bill Boggs - debate, Hoffman v. Graham (Box AV3)
      - OR68. 1986 Mar. 2, "On the Issues" cable access television (show 4), with Carol Bellamy (Box AV3)
      - OR69. 1986 Mar. 21, "On the Issues" cable access television (show 8), "Feminists vs. Censorship," with Susie Orbach and reporter Nan Hunter (Box AV3)
      - OR70. Circa 1986, "On the Issues" show, advertisement and presentation tape, 11 minutes (Box AV3)
      - OR71. Undated, "Straight Talk" ["Merle Hoffman/Martha Lean/Rosenberg"] (Box AV3)
    - VHS Videocassettes, circa 1982-1998
      Some titles listed also duplicated in the U-Matic videocassettes subseries. In chronological order.
      [Originals closed to use. No use copies are currently available. However, some preservation copies of U-Matic duplicates exist, from which use copies can be made. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use the collection.]
      - Originals OR72-80 (CLOSED) (Box AV3)
      - OR72. Circa 1982, "Abortion: A Different Light" documentary, produced by Merle Hoffman, 28 minutes (Box AV4)
      - OR73. 1986 Feb. 9, "On the Issues" cable access television (show 1), guests Bella Abzug and Carla Jackson (Box AV4)
      - OR74. 1986 Feb. 16, "On the Issues" cable access television (show 2), guests Baird/Brown and Matusinka (Box AV4)
      - OR75. 1986 Mar. 21, "On the Issues" cable access television (show 8), "Body Image," with Susie Orbach (Box AV4)
      - OR76. 1986 Apr. 2, "On the Issues" cable access television (show 9), "Women and the Criminal Justice System," with Elizabeth Holtzman (Box AV4)
      - OR77. 1990, Phyllis Chesler birthday celebration, "raw footage - 2 hours" (Box AV4)
      - OR78. 1995 May 24, 25 Years of Choices, "Choices 'Meded,'" 14 minutes [incomplete and slightly damaged] (Box AV4)
      - OR79. 1998 May 13, Dr. Martin Gold's 80th birthday (Box AV4)
      - OR80. 1990s, "The Abortion Pill" documentary, produced by Marion Lipschutz and Rose Rosenblatt (Box AV4)
    - U-Matic Video Cassettes
      Includes a number of recordings of Hoffman's cable access shows, "Choices" and "On the Issues." In original, unarranged order.
      [Originals closed to use. No use copies currently available. Preservation copies have been made on DVD from which use copies can be made, but these are closed to general use - see Box AV9. Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use the collection.]
      - Originals, OR-Tapes 1-14 (CLOSED) (Box AV4)
      - OR-Tape1. "Abortion: A Different Light" (1982); Response to "The Silent Scream", Planned Parenthood of Seattle-King County, (1985); "Choices," Reel #4 (1981). (Box AV5)
      - OR-Tape2. "Coca Crystal," 1984 Jan. 11 (Box AV5)
        [TRT 60:00.]
      - OR-Tape3. "Choices," Reel #19, Debates. Undated (Box AV5)
      - OR-Tape4. "Choices," Reel#9, "Office Getaways" (undated); "Broadcast Plaza Kennedy Rape" (1991). (Box AV5)
        [TRT 120:00.]
      - OR-Tape5. "Abortion: A Different Light," 1982. (Box AV6)
      - OR-Tape6. "Merle Hoffman: On the Issues," Show #6, "The Women's Movement: The Second Stage," with Betty Friedan (undated); "Merle Hoffman: On the Issues," Show #7, "Family and Divorce," with Phyllis Chesler (undated). (Box AV6)
      - OR-Tape7. "Merle Hoffman: On the Issues," Show #8, "Fat is a Feminist Issue," with Susan Orbach (undated); "Merle Hoffman: On the Issues," Show #9, "Women and the Criminal Justice System," with Elizabeth Holtzman (undated). (Box AV6)
      - OR-Tape8. "Hoffman (1995 May 3)"; "Choices," Titles and Credits (undated). (Box AV6)
      - OR-Tape9. "Merle Hoffman: On the Issues," Show #1, with: Bella Abzug and Karla Jackson, NY Women Against Rape (1986 Feb. 5, aired Sept. 28); "Merle Hoffman: On the Issues," Show #2, with: Jennifer Brown - NOW-NYC President, Bill Baird - Reproductive Rights Crusader, Alexandra Matusinda - Women Against Pornography (1986 Feb. 13). (Box AV7)
      - OR-Tape10. "Merle Hoffman: On the Issues," Show #3, "Women in Religion, with: Rabbi Julie Gordon; Rev. Lucinda Liard-Kuhn (undated); "Merle Hoffman: On the Issues," Show #4, "Women in Politics," with Carol Bellany, former NYC Council President (undated). (Box AV7)
      - OR-Tape11."Merle Hoffman: On the Issues," Show #5, "Aging," with Myrna Lewis, Mt. Sinai School of Medicine; Deborah Perry, Feminist Witch. (Box AV7)
        [TRT 30:00.]
      - OR-Tape12. AM New York, "Choices," Reel #2, Sarah Weddington (1981 Dec. 9); "Choices," Reel #15 (undated); "Choices," Reel #18 (undated). (Box AV7)
      - OR-Tape13. "Choices," Reel #20 (undated); "Choices," Reel #21 (undated); 10pm News, "Over the Counter Contraception" (undated). (Box AV8)
        [TRT 50:00.]
      - OR-Tape14. "Broadcast Plaza - Clinton Affair," 1992 Jan. 27 (Box AV8)
      - U-Matic Tapes Preservation Copies: Disks PC1-14 (Restricted) (Box AV9)
        [Format: DVD. Source: OR-Tapes-1-14. Created 2006.]
        [Closed to general reference use. For creating use copies only.]
- Ephemera Series, circa 1985-1991 and undated, 4 boxes
  - Choices condoms, undated (Box E1)
  - "I'm pro-choice and I shoot back!" button, undated (Box E1)
  - "Women's Week" button [removed from Suffolk Community College speech file], 1991 (Box E1)
  - On the Issues buttons - "Feminist Government in Exile," undated (Box E1)
  - Stuffed teddy bear, undated (Box E2)
- Oversize Materials, 5 boxes, 3 folders
  - Oversize Boxes
    - Choices Series, 1977-1998 and undated
      - Subject Files Subseries, 1978-1996 and undated
        - Abortion Files: Female Health Topics and Diagnostics Reporter with articles on Choices and on the National Abortion Federation, 1979 (Oversize-box OS1)
        - Research Files: Statistics - Health coverage type by neighborhood and procedure, 1991-1995 (Oversize-box OS1)
        - Research Files: Statistics - Patient age (gynecology), 1993-1995 and undated (Oversize-box OS1)
        - Research Files: Statistics - Patient age (termination of pregnancy), 1993-1995 and undated (Oversize-box OS1)
        - General Subject Files: Cancer treatment program presentation, undated (Oversize-box OS1)
        - General Subject Files: Choices newsletter Interaction - layout, 1978 and 1981 (Oversize-box OS1)
        - General Subject Files: Conference - National Latinas Caucus - Vision newsletter, 1992 Feb.-Mar. (Oversize-box OS1)
        - General Subject Files: Rape Treatment Program presentation - poster, 1996 (Oversize-box OS1)
      - Outreach Subseries, 1983
        - Choices Health Fair poster layout, 1983 (Oversize-box OS1)
      - Staff Files Subseries, 1993-1995
        - Joy Silver (marketing) - marketing reports and utilization statistics, 1993-1995 (Oversize-box OS1)
      - Marketing Subseries, circa 1982-1998 and undated
        - Choices calendar - layout sheets, 1988, 3 folders (Oversize-box OS1)
        - Choices posters, undated (Oversize-box OS1)
        - Marketing statistics - referral sources, 1992-1995, 1998, 2 folders (Oversize-box OS1)
        - New logo and letterhead, 1996 (Oversize-box OS1)
        - Pamphlet and advertisement layout sheets, 1983-1984 and undated (Oversize-box OS1)
        - Pamphlet and advertisement layout sheets, 1983 and 1988 (Oversize-box OS2)
        - Pamphlet layout sheets, circa 1982, 2 folders (Oversize-box OS2)
        - Pamphlet layout sheets, undated (Oversize-box OS2)
        - Utilization statistics and marketing plan - physician referral statistics, 1990 (Oversize-box OS2)
      - Operations Subseries, 1977-1994 and undated
        - Facilities Files
          - Relocation and lease - blueprints, 1977 (Oversize-box OS2)
          - Architectural blueprints, 1977 and undated (Oversize-box OS2)
          - Richard Hein Architects, 1987-1989 and undated (Oversize-box OS2)
          - Queens neighborhoods - locations of other health facilities, circa 1990 (Oversize-box OS2)
          - Renovations, 1992 and undated (Oversize-box OS2)
        - Personnel Files
          - Analysis of hours worked in telephone room, 1988 (Oversize-box OS2)
          - Business Office - personnel and contractor expenses, 1989 and undated (Oversize-box OS2)
        - General Operations Files
          - Accreditation Association for Ambulatory Health Care Providers certificate, 1989 (Oversize-box OS2)
          - Pre-natal care policies and patients - patient visits, 1990 (Oversize-box OS2)
          - Financial statements, 1994 (Oversize-box OS2)
    - On the Issues Series, circa 1982-1998 and undated
      - Editorial Files Subseries, 1993 and undated
        - Blue Stocking, vol. 1, no. 6, 1993 June (Oversize-box OS2)
        - Cartoon - "Heartbroke," undated (Oversize-box OS2)
        - New Directions for Women sample issues, 1993 (Oversize-box OS2)
      - Marketing Subseries, circa 1982-1990s and undated
        - "Feminist Government in Exile" - portion of felt banner, undated (Oversize-box OS2)
        - On the Issues advertisements - layout, circa 1989 and undated, 2 folders (Oversize-box OS3)
        - On the Issues poster, 1990s (Oversize-box OS3)
        - Pamphlet layout sheet, circa 1982 (Oversize-box OS3)
      - Production and Distribution Subseries, 1992-1998 and undated
        - Production by Issue
          - Winter 1992 issue, cover art (Oversize-box OS3)
          - Spring 1993 issue, mounted cover art (Oversize-box OS3)
          - Summer 1998 issue, proofs and blues (Oversize-box OS3)
        - Production by Issue (Oversize-box OS4)
          - Fall 1998 issue, proofs (Oversize-box OS4)
        - Production by Subject
          - Artwork, undated (Oversize-box OS4)
          - Central Books distribution reports, 1997-1998 (Oversize-box OS4)
      - Administration Subseries, circa 1993
        - Budget - Expenses, circa 1993 (Oversize-box OS4)
    - Personal Series, circa 1982-1996
      - Writings and Speeches Subseries, circa 1982-1980s
        - "Abortion: A Different Light" documentary announcement - layout sheet, circa 1982 (Oversize-box OS4)
        - "On the Issues" cable access show - videotapes - layout for advertisement, 1980s (Oversize-box OS4)
      - Subject Files Subseries, 1990
        - Abortion Files: NOW-NYS News and NOW-NYS Action Report, 1990 (Oversize-box OS4)
      - Politics and Activism Subseries, 1996
        - Refuse and Resist! National Day of Appreciation for Abortion Providers - award to Merle Hoffman, 1996 (Oversize-box OS4)
      - New York Pro-Choice Coalition Subseries, 1985-1989
        - Minutes and Meeting Materials Files: Freedom Socialist newspaper, 1985 Summer (Oversize-box OS4)
        - Minutes and Meeting Materials Files: 1989 Sept. 5 meeting, New Youth Connections newspaper, 1989 May (Oversize-box OS4)
        - General New York Pro-Choice Coalition Files: Bank statements, 1987 July-1989 Sept. (Oversize-box OS4)
        - General New York Pro-Choice Coalition Files: Income and expense summary, 1988 (Oversize-box OS4)
      - General Personal Files Subseries, 1983-1987
        - Who's Who certificates of inclusion, 1983-1987 (Oversize-box OS4)
    - Photographic Materials Series, circa 1984-1998 and undated
      - Choices Subseries, undated
        - Subject Files: Cancer program presentation - contact sheets, undated (Oversize-box OS5)
        - Personnel Files: Employee of the Year award presentation, undated (Oversize-box OS5)
        - Marketing: Clinic scenes, mounted for printing, undated, 4 folders (Oversize-box OS5)
      - On the Issues Subseries, 1980s-1998
        - Marketing: On the Issues advertisement layout, 1980s (Oversize-box OS5)
        - Marketing: On the Issues advertisement layout - photograph of New York Pro-Choice Coalition rally, 1980s (Oversize-box OS5)
        - Production by Issue: Summer 1998 issue, proofs - "pg. 1 old" (Oversize-box OS5)
        - Production by Issue: Fall 1998 issue
          - Proofs for advertisements, 2 folders (Oversize-box OS5)
          - Proofs - "Old p. 34" (Oversize-box OS5)
          - Proofs - "Old p. 35" (Oversize-box OS5)
      - Personal Subseries, circa 1984 and undated
        - Politics and Activism: Merle Hoffman with Geraldine Ferraro, circa 1984 (Oversize-box OS5)
        - General Personal
          - Merle Hoffman portraits, undated (Oversize-box OS5)
          - Merle Hoffman with her horse, undated (Oversize-box OS5)
          - Merle Hoffman with Ruth Hoffman, Bess Myerson and others at formal party - contact sheets, undated (Oversize-box OS5)
    - Ephemera Series, circa 1985-1990 and undated
      - On the Issues felt banner - "Feminist Government in Exile," undated (Oversize-box E3)
      - New York Pro-Choice Coalition vinyl banners, circa 1985-1990 (Oversize-box E4)
  - Folders in Oversize Cabinets
    - Choices Series, 1988-1992 and undated
      - Facilities Subseries, 1988-1992 and undated (Oversize-folder 1)
        - Blueprint [removed from 1992 Renovations file], 1990 (Oversize-folder 1)
      - Facilities (Oversize-folder 2)
        - Blueprint, "Demolition Plan" [removed from 1992 Renovations file], 1990 (Oversize-folder 2)
        - Blueprint, "Floor Plan," 1990 (Oversize-folder 2)
        - Architectural drawing, "Lefrak Center," undated (Oversize-folder 2)
      - Facilities (Oversize-folder 3)
        - Blueprint, "'Choices's Sk. 7," 1988 Jan. 22 (Oversize-folder 3)
        - Blueprint, "'Choices's Sk. 8," 1988 Feb. 9 (Oversize-folder 3)
        - Blueprint, "'Choices's Sk. 9," 1988 Mar. 8 (Oversize-folder 3)
        - Blueprint, "'Choices's Sk. 9," 1988-1989 (Oversize-folder 3)
        - Blueprint, "Sk. 5," undated (Oversize-folder 3)
        - Blueprint, undated (Oversize-folder 3)
- Accessions (2004-0041) and (2004-0062), 50 boxes
  The additions (04-041 and 04-062) (18,750 items, 30 linear feet; dated 1971-2003) consists primarily of administrative and financial files from Choices Women's Medical Center and predecessor clinics, including correspondence, financial reports, public relations and media files, board meeting files, policy and procedure manuals, subject files, insurance files, program files, grants files, legal files, and files related to ON THE ISSUES magazine. Also included are a small number of Hoffman's personal writings. This accession is unprocessed and closed to researchers.
- Accession (2005-0023), 20 boxes
  Addition (05-023) (5150 items, 12 lin. ft; dated 1978-2003) consists primarily of administrative and financial records from Choices Women's Medical Center, including correspondence, financial reports, public relations and media files. Also includes board meeting, subject, insurance, program, legal and grant files, as well as policy and procedure manuals; 33 videotapes, 84 slides, 54 photographs and contact sheets; 1 CD-ROM; printed materials; and promotional calendars. Accession is unprocessed and closed to researchers.
- Accession (2012-0049), dated 1978-2012 and undated, 7 boxes
  Files from the office of Merle Hoffman. Includes correspondence, legal and financial files, meeting agendas and minutes, reports, blueprints and other physical plant materials, research files, and documentation of her work with various staff members, vendors, and others both at Choices and within the context of publishing On The Issues. Materials have been arranged alphabetically.
  - 41st Avenue Realty, 1996-1998, 2002, 2004 (Box 1)
  - AAAHC (Accreditation Association for Ambulatory Health Care Inc.), 2004 (Box 1)
  - Abbot, Sidney, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Abbelson, Gerri, 1995, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Abortionomics, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Abortion Rights, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Abzug, Liz, 1995-1996 and undated (Box 1)
  - Adam, Bill, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Animal Hospital, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Appointment Books, 1987-1988, 1992, 1999, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Architecture for Health, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Architecture for Health, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Asparo, Carmine, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Bader, Eleanor (Elinor), 1999, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Barovack, Harriett, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Bates, Leandra, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Berger, Ted, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Bronstein, Karen, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Brooklyn Ambulatory Surgery Center, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Cease & Desist Papers, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Chernoff, Alexander, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Chesler, Phyllis, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Choices Calendar of Women's Wisdom, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Choices Correspondence (includes legal items and insurance matters), 1986-1988, 1994, 1996-1998 (Box 2)
  - Choices, Team Directions for Managers and Supervisors, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Choices, meetings with staff, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Clinic, 1st Floor Plans, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Columbia University, 2004 (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive, 2005 (Box 2)
  - Construx Legal File, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Chron, Sept. 1999 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - Court T.V., 2003 (Box 2)
  - Davidoff & Malito LLP; Attorneys at Law, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Davis, B., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Decorating, 1990 (Box 2)
  - DeKaye, Allan, undated (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation, 2000, 2006, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation: Black Perle-Nicole Browne, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation: Pornography Awareness-Andrew Dworkin, 1993, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation: Friends of Animals Event, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation: Grants, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation: Guide Dog Foundation for the Blind, Inc., 2002 (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation: Letterhead & Envelope, undated (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation: Maria Namiiro, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation: New York Latinas Against Domestic Violence, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation: NOW-NYC, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Diana Foundation: THEA, Inc., 2003 (Box 2)
  - DiGiorgio Associates, Inc., 1996 (Box 2)
  - Directors Minutes, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Disorders of Intimacy Paradigm, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Dreier, 2004 (Box 2)
  - Dreier-AHAC, 2004 (Box 2)
  - Dreier-LLP, 2005 (Box 2)
  - Dreier/Zeiss, 2005 (Box 2)
  - Dubow, Alan, 2005 (Box 2)
  - Duke University: Gift Agreement, 2000, 2003 (Box 2)
  - East Hampton: 108 Runnymeade drive, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Elahi, Dr. E. Hakim, 1997-1998 (Box 3)
  - Elmhurst Hospital Center, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Expressions of Support for Choices Women's Medical Center, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Fan Mail, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Farrell, Annette C., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Federal Lawsuit, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Federal Realty, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Feminist Seder, undated (Box 3)
  - Fino, Charles, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Floor Plans, undated (Box 3)
  - French Documentary, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Furniture and Interior Design, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Gardasil, 2007 (Box 3)
  - Garfunkel, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Garrison, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Garrison House, 2002 (Box 3)